trademarks411.com 2019-05-06

# Trademarks411.com | Privacy Policy

  1. **Our Commitment to Privacy.** This notice describes our Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy is designed to advise you about how we collect, use, and protect the personal information you provide. By visiting this site or sites that link to this privacy policy or by using our mobile applications, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

  2. **What Information is Collected.**

(a) Information You Provide to Us: We collect any information you enter on our site or in our mobile applications, or that you give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of our services and features.

(b) Automatic Information: When you visit a website or mobile application, you disclose certain information, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the time of your visit. This site or in our mobile applications, like many other sites and mobile applications, records this basic information about visits to our site and in our mobile applications.

(c) "Cookies": Cookies are pieces of information that are transferred to your computer from a web server. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or to refuse to accept cookies.

  3. **How and When the Information is Used.** The information we collect is used for administering our business activities. We may use the information to notify you about changes to our website, mobile application, new services, or special offers. If you do not wish to receive such information, you may unsubscribe from our promotions list on any one of the promotions we send to you.

  4. **How We Protect Your Information.** The privacy and protection of your information is important to us. We do not make any personal information available to third parties without your permission unless we are required by law to comply with a valid legal requirement such as applicable law, government regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order. Your access to some services and content is password protected. We advise that you do not disclose your password to anyone. In addition, we recommend you sign out of password-protected services at the end of your session.

  5. **Who Has Access to the Information.** Information about our users is important to us. We will not disclose any individually identifiable information to any third party without first receiving that user's permission. You should be aware, however, that the US Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO) will make public the names and addresses of trademark applicants.

  6. **Methods We Use to Protect Your Information and Limitation of Our Liability for Lost or Stolen Data.** We use security software to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. In addition, our business practices are reviewed periodically for compliance with policies and procedures governing the security and confidentiality of our information. Our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons. However, every security system and measure is subject to breach and loss, misuse, destruction, dissemination and alteration of your personal information may occur and should it occur we will have no liability to you or to any third party arising out of any loss, misuse, destruction, or alternation of your data.

  7. **Children.** This website and our mobile application does not provide services or sell products to children under the age of 18. If you are under 18, you may use this website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

  8. **How You Can Access Your Information.** You can request access to all your personally identifiable information by sending an e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#88e1e6eee7c8fcfae9ecede5e9fae3fbbcb9b9a6ebe7e5 "info@trademarks411.com") and requesting access to all your personally identifiable information.

  9. **Consent.** By using our website or mobile application, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

  10. **Third Party Sites.** We may maintain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we are not responsible for the Privacy Practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

  11. **Changes to Privacy Policy.** If our Privacy Policy or procedures change, we will immediately post those changes to our website. Any such changes will be effective immediately upon being posted, unless otherwise stated in the change.

  12. **Effective Date.** This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 1, 2007.
